I broke another one. Sprout,
>> let me give you a hand after I'm done
with this.
>> Quit being such a silly little boy.
>> Can I try flipping one, too?
>> I think we should do it together, Lou.
You've been clumsy as a [__] all
morning.
What is it? A problem when I touch you
like this?
>> No, it's fine. Totally fine, Sprout.
>> You know what, Louie? You are a very
cool friend.
>> Friend? Oh. Uh, yeah. Friend.
>> If I didn't already have a personal
[__] like Cozmo, someone like you with
your big balloon butt cheeks would
totally be on the table for me.
Okay, I'm going to make like diarrhea
and blow out of this [__] hole before
Yatada and Blog get here.
>> Why so fast? They're just my housemates.
They're not going to think we're dating
if that's what you're scared of. They
don't even know I like boys. I don't
need other tunes seeing us eat breakfast
together and deciding we're a thing.
We're just eating eggs.
The sexiest strawberry in Garden View
eating breakfast with the biggest
anxietyfilled balloon bottom [__] in
the neighborhood. What else would they
think?
>> Well, you don't have to be so scared
that you hit me.
>> Me scared? Everyone in Garden View
already knows I'm gay. You're the one
who's trying to make this thing we got
between us something more than it
actually is. Like you want to show me
off to your friends or some [__] Don't
act like I ain't catching on.
>> I would never TRY TO SHOW YOU OFF.
>> YEAH, you would. Cuz you've got nothing.
>> We're friends. I get you want to be
nothing more. I accepted that a long
time ago. Get out of my house.
>> This is my house. You leave.
>> I'll do that. But the next time we make
omelets, you'd better have actual
butter. None of that margarine [__]
Come on, lady boy. Hop on the bike.
Did you have fun today, Sprout? Shut up.
Can we stop by Crispy Cream Donuts on
the way home? I got you, fat ass. But
first, let's ride by Dy's house. I want
to see if he's outside so I can mess
with him. The perfect day for Garden
View's most handsomest flower to be
outside with his iPad. Look, Sprout,
there he is. A Yeah. Take this rock and
throw it at him as hard as you can.
Won't that hurt him? That's the point,
Cosmo. We're going to crack his skull
open.
What are you pulling that money out for?
You want to give that to me in exchange
for a kiss? Oh, come on. Not you, too. I
sure am popular. You know, you're far
from the first tune I kissed today.
Would you really be fine with secondhand
goods?
Wow, that's a lot of money. I'm totally
being put on the spot here. But this is
what it means being the star of the show
after all. A true star has got to please
everyone when the opportunity arises.
You know, you're far from the first tune
I kissed today. Would you really be fine
with secondhand goods?
>> What the hell is Dandy doing?
>> Howdy, fellow mans. And a good morning
to you,
>> Dandy. Why are you sitting at a kissing
booth?
>> Daddy's iPad broke, so Daddy needs to
make money to buy a new one. Wow,
Dandelicious. I didn't take you for such
a boy kisser. How dare you frame it in
such a sinful way. Kissing boys with
passion is what God looks down upon, not
for being a working tune. What sprout
means is you couldn't think of literally
any other way to make money.
>> Why couldn't you just sell lemonade or
some [__]
>> Do I look like I know how to make
lemonade, [__]
>> What if you kiss a tune and they, you
know, get the wrong idea?
>> Astro baby girl, these kisses are purely
transactional. I make that very clear on
the sign.
NO,
>> YOU'RE SELLING your soft, sweet kisses
for a dollar. I didn't take you for such
a boy kisser dandy.
>> That's what I said.
>> Oh, the other tunes are going to get
such a kick out of this when I tell them
you're one of them sissies.
>> Shrimpo, my motto is unless they're
paying your bills, pay them [__] no
mind. So, if you aren't buying a kiss, I
think it'd be best for you to go.
>> I didn't say that. Obviously, I'm going
to partake because a badass shrimpo
never backs down from a challenge.
>> Wow, a dollar. Couldn't even afford the
more spicy of the two options.
>> Do not judge me for taking advantage.
You're the one being a [__] for cheap
pay.
>> Hey, uh, cool it there, big man. This is
my first kiss of the day.
>> I'm getting my money's worth, so you
shut up. You're going to say no homo
after we do this cuz I don't need no
tunes running around spreading rumors
that we hold hands in secret or some
[__] You got that?
>> You think I'm ecstatic about this whole
thing myself?
>> What was that? You should be grateful to
have me twink. I've been saving my first
kiss for someone special and you ain't
[__]
Should we go there? You got what you
paid for plus a little extra? Now beat
it and make sure to spread word to the
tunes around town that their star is
down for anything for the right price.
Wait, you're telling me it's this easy
to make money in Garden View? I didn't
know we were surrounded by so many boy
kissers.
>> To be a boy kisser is many a tunes
nature. Sprout, whatever you're
thinking, for the love of God, do not do
it.
>> What are you doing?
>> Counting my dollar. What's Sprout doing?
>> I'm afraid you've got competition,
Dandy.
>> That dirty strawberry. Look how many
he's already got.
>> I hear that everyone was camped out
outside his house last night in
anticipation.
>> You mean he was planning this?
>> Oh, no. Tunes are always just camping
out there, waiting for the day this
would inevitably come.
>> He's already made $20,000.
Astro, go over there and give him a
piece of my mind.
>> Sprout, I'm busy making money. Go away.
>> Dandy told us to come over and give you
a piece of his mind, but I don't know
what to say.
>> Astro, shut up. I've got to do this.
Dandy is my rival.
>> Why do you and Dandy always say that?
Rivals at what?
>> I don't know. We're just rivals. Okay.
Maybe it's cuz we're plants. I don't
know. I don't give a [__]
>> Well, it's weird.
>> Listen, if I'm not better than Dandy at
everything, then I might as well be good
at nothing.
>> Girl, that doesn't even make sense.
>> Who's next?
Uh, hi, Sprout. Oh. Uh, Lou, what are
you doing here? Well, I'm here to buy
one of your sloppy kisses, of course.
Just cause it be funny to see a straight
guy like me kissing another guy.
Totally. Not because I'm gay or
anything. We all know I'm not one of
them queers. Right. Right. I like girls
in their tits.
>> I told you not to come by my house
today, Louie. Cosmo has the day off from
work. He can see you from here.
>> Well, when you dropped by my house this
morning for breakfast, it was unexpected
as [__] I just had to tell you how much
fun I had. And I'm sorry if I came off
as clingy at the time. But again, we
can't stress it enough here that I DON'T
LIKE BOYS. I LIKE GIRLS with huge
knockers.
Dandy, I want my dollar back.
>> You got what you paid for Shrimpo.
>> I want to get a Milky Way out of the
vending machine down the street. Give it
to me now.
>> I gave you a $20 bill to kiss me in
front of my friends and make me look
like a hot commodity. So just use that.
I don't have it anymore. I already spent
it on a bunch of Milky Ways.
Lou, can you go home? I don't appreciate
you lying about me in front of all our
friends just because you're a lonely
tune. I have never hung out with you
once in my life.
>> What kind of sounds do a strawberry and
a balloon make when they [__]
>> If I give each of you $1, will you leave
me alone?
>> Yes. Yes.
>> Yes.
>> Hi, Dandy. Where's the dollar you got
from Shrimpo?
>> He punched me in my eye and then took it
back.
>> Oh, I'm sorry.
>> Astro, why do the good tunes always
suffer?
>> I don't know.
>> Perhaps God just hates to see a bad
[__] succeed.
>> Now, Dandy, don't let this dim your
belief in God. This is but a fleeting
moment passing in time. Astro, can you
patronize me?
>> You mean like how you are the most
special one-of-a-kind flower in all of
Garden View?
>> Thanks. I needed that up in this [__]
>> So, you haven't made any money all day.
>> Garden View is in the middle of an
inflation. Astro, obviously, in this
[__] economy, I don't blame them for
holding on to their money, even if it
means the star of the show like me isn't
getting the attention I rightfully
deserve. You know,
>> you're so kind. Well, you know, Dandy, I
got a dollar. Maybe I could get one of
your sweet kisses.
>> I don't need the money so bad that I
take a dollar away from my best friend.
>> Oh, it wouldn't be taking anything away
from me. Here, I'll stand in front of
the booth just like a customer.
One of your finest kisses, please.
>> One of my finest, huh? Well, I'll see
what I can do for a dollar. Just don't
expect anything extravagant.
>> Golly, that's fine. Anything you give me
will be special.
Does my breath stink like [__]
>> It's too weird since we're friends. I'm
sorry.
>> Oh,
>> I'm keeping your dollar though because I
still need to buy an iPad.
>> Sprout. What is ALL THIS?
Stop right there, Lou. I said you're not
allowed to come around here anymore
after I caught you two sneaking around
the last time. Cosmo, it's not what it
looks like. Louie was just here as a
friend. It's a lemonade stand. A
lemonade stand with benefits more like
it. Do you know how many calls I've been
getting from tunes who want you sliding
into their bed this evening?
Dead ass. Sprout. I'm going to unal
alive you. Please, you've got to listen
to me. Whatever they're saying on the
phone, they're lying to you, babe. All
these fake ass [__] don't know what
they're saying. I've never been anything
but faithful. What does the sign say?
I don't got to show you [__] Oh, yes
you do. No, I'm going inside. I got
oatmeal cookies in the oven. I can't be
dealing with this. It's Dy's fault. You
know how much I got to upstage that
rainbow petal dork. Why do you always
have to ruin Dandy's day? He never does
anything to you. He makes faces at me
when others aren't looking. Look, he's
doing it right now. Go apologize to him
right now or you are not getting any
oatmeal cookies. And take all this stuff
down and tell everyone to go home. I
don't need a bunch of pickme tunes in
front of my house.
>> Okay, good. What do you want for dinner,
hun? Baked potatoes. I'll start putting
out the fixings. What about me? I've got
something special for home wreckers like
you.
>> Holy [__] Ah.
>> Hey, Dandy. What are you doing? What's
it look like? I'm packing up. How much
money did you make today? I don't know.
Like a dollar that I stole from Astro.
Oh, that's not enough for an iPad. It's
whatever. Well, it's not whatever. What
are you going to do before bed tonight
then? Since you usually play games on
your iPad, I'll just do something else
tonight, like clean my toilet since it's
backed up with a lot of poopy. That
doesn't sound fun. I wanted to
apologize. Dead ass. Or is Cosmo making
you do it? A little bit of both. Well,
tell Cosmo thanks for trying.
How much were you charging for kisses
again? A dollar. I know my worth.
Sprout, don't say that. if you feel like
staying open for another minute. I was
thinking that maybe I could, you know,
buy a uh uh buy a uh buy a, you know,
buy a couple from you.
I need like $67 more if I want to buy a
new iPad. A couple wouldn't do. Then
you're in luck. I got $20,000, so you
better be ready to put your tongue where
it belongs. 20,000 times. You got
chapstick? No. Well, go buy some and
apply that [__] cuz you're going to need
it. Okay, I'm ready. Are you ready?
Yeah, I'm ready. Are you sure you are? I
think so.
What the hell is that? Look. I'm sorry.
It's just the thought of kissing you is
making me sick. Do you want a new iPad
or not? How many times do we got to do
this again? I can just turn and leave,
you know. Okay, okay, just lean in and
do it before I change my mind.
Did you just vomit in your mouth and
swallow it? No, I freaking heard it. No,
you didn't, Dweeb. I swear if you blow
chunks in my mouth.
Are you serious? Why does your breath
taste like Cosmo's ass? What do you
godamn think? You knew what you were
signing up for. Are you done throwing up
yet? Yeah. Well, clean yourself up,
dweeb, cuz you know I still got $19,999
more dollars.
>> The green beans are ready. Dig in, fart
boxes.
>> Can I please have just a couple more
green beans, you guys?
>> What the hell did you just say to Yada?
You want to repeat that?
>> Yeah. You want to repeat that?
>> Why do I always get next to nothing
compared to you? cuz I bought this can
of seasoned green beans with my money.
>> You can have an equal amount of food
when you can provide an equal amount of
money. You're lucky you're getting any
at all after you took my eggs right out
of the fridge this morning. Sprout came
to visit and he wanted breakfast.
>> Sprout was here again in the apartment
that only me and Blot are paying for and
not you.
>> You know he's gay, right? You gay too,
Balloon Boy?
>> No. No, I'm normal. I'm straight.
Now he's crying like a poopy baby. Can't
even enjoy my green beans up in this
[__]
>> Why do you two always have to yell at
me?
>> Because we hate you. Everybody hates
you. All you do is be annoying and
autistic.
>> We're the circus trio. You can't say
that about me.
>> We stopped being the circus trio when we
ran away from the circus and blot
started working at Dollar Tree and I
opened my own nationwide food chain,
Goss Tacos. You don't do anything,
Louie. You don't work. You don't go to
school.
>> I've got social anxiety. What am I
supposed to do?
>> That's it. Mama's getting the
thumbtacks.
>> No, no, no, no, no. Not those again.
>> Take one of those and poke yourself.
>> Do it so we can be done with you. Pop
yourself.
>> Yeah, pop yourself.
>> Pop yourself.
See, he can't even do that. See you
later, you fart blasters. I'm going
across the street to Dollar Tree to buy
a frozen burrito. Cuz unlike you, Louie,
I've actually got money.
>> I'm going in the bathroom to take some
bubbly poops. Don't come crying to be
about your depression, Lou. I'm sick of
hearing it.
I'm so bad. What are you doing, Cosmo?
>> Oh, you know, just taking out the trash.
Well, put my phone down and start
putting the fixings on your baked potato
before it gets cold.
Are you still awake, Louie?
You scared me, Astro. I'm sorry.
>> Do you have a good dream prepared for me
tonight?
>> It's why I'm here. You look like you
need it.
>> I I really do.
>> You look cold. Let me help cover you up.
Sorry.
>> No, I'm sorry for my ass being so fat.
Astro, would your life be easier if I
just pop myself?
>> Oh, baby boy, why would you say that?
>> I'm anxious about everything. So surely
you have to put extra effort into my
dreams to make me happy. And if you go
around giving everyone in town dreams,
then surely if one tune were to
disappear, your job would be a whole lot
easier at night. Well, if you were gone,
then I wouldn't have an extra friend
during the day.
Thanks. It makes me happy to know at
least there's one tune in this world who
isn't put off by my existence. Before I
go into a makebelieve world where I can
pretend to be loved, Astro, the way you
can give all us tunes whatever dreams we
want, can you do the same for yourself?
Because it's not fair if you can't. I
admit I don't sleep very often since a
lot of my time is making sure everyone
else has good ones. But I'll be fine,
just like you will.
>> Good night, Astro, for whenever you do
go to sleep tonight.
>> Good night, Louie. Sweet dreams. I'll
make sure your ones tomorrow are twice
as pleasant.
Louis's right. It's no fair. My tune
ability doesn't let me give myself good
dreams like I can do so for everybody
else. But if I can make another version
of myself happy in their dreams, even if
I can't experience that happiness
myself, then maybe that's enough.
Oh, hey [__] I didn't see you there.
I'm Yada from the hit Roblox game
Dandy's World. I'm on my way to work at
my restaurant's Yato's Tacos. How did
you like today's episode? Did you think
it was bitching? That's cool. I thought
it was [__] cuz I was only in it for
like a minute. Hey, if you thought it
was cool as [__] though, you should
support Tamers 1 2 3 4 5 by joining his
Patreon. You can find deleted scenes and
a bunch of gifts that were used in this
episode and all the previous ones. And
also tell him which tunes you want to
see videos centered around next. That's
it. Mama Yatta need to go to work at
Yato's Tacos.
[__] I want to leave this town.
See the world with you.
Only angry looks and frowns. I don't
care when it's us too.
Desert towns and a road cafes
boots up on the dash.
Cross the roads towards LA.
Forget about the past.
Let's leave in the moment.
We'll be on the interstate.
Life around is boring.
Let's just get away. pain.
We're on a oneway trip to hell if I know
half a pack of cigarettes on an open
road.
Left fan at 12:00,
right hand on yours.
Once the radio cuts out, we'll roll the
door.
Let's leave in the morning.
We'll be on the interstate.
Laugh around this boring.
Let's just get away. Hey, let's leave in
the morning.
We'll be on the interstate.
Life around is boring.
Let's just get away. Hey.